listafterlist.com 2016-12-13

# Privacy Policy | ListAfterList

We respect your privacy. This privacy policy describes how we treat personal information when you use the Web sites, services and offerings of ListAfterList.com and our affiliated services (“LISTAFTERLIST”).

**Personal Information**

  * Registering with us is optional. When you register with us and interact with our Web sites, services and offerings, you provide us with information that is personally identified with you. Depending on how you interact with our services, this information may include:  
registration-related information,  such as, name, e-mail address, Lister Name (your user ID for the service), address, or gender, or profile related information (such as location, occupation, industry, astrological sign, personal “about me” descriptions;
  * information about your visits to LISTAFTERLIST, and your responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on these Web sites;
  * information about the searches you perform through LISTAFTERLIST and how you use the results of those searches;
  * information about LISTAFTERLIST services or offerings that you use;
  * transaction-related information, such as, e-mail inquiries to us, payment information for purchases, billing or shipping information, or a history of products purchased through LISTAFTERLIST;
  * customer service information about you as a LISTAFTERLIST user or subscriber; or
  * other information specifically related to your use of a particular LISTAFTERLIST service or offering.

Your LISTAFTERLIST information may be supplemented with additional information from other companies. Your LISTAFTERLIST information may also include certain technical information gathered or received when you use LISTAFTERLIST, such as, Internet protocol address, information about your geographic location and the domain name of your Internet service provider.  
LISTAFTERLIST will use the Lister Name, or similar technologies, to authenticate you on LISTAFTERLIST and enable you to take advantage of web site offerings.

**Use of Information**

We may use your information:

  * to provide our services to you and to improve our services;
  * to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you;
  * to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services;
  * to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;
  * to conduct research about your use of LISTAFTERLIST; and
  * to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest.

**Information Sharing**

We will not share your information with third parties unless:

  * you agree to receive special promotional offers via email from ListAfterList.com and their trusted partners by opting-in during registration;
  * it is necessary to fulfill a transaction you have requested;
  * in circumstances in which you have consented to the sharing of your information;
  * we believe we are required to do so by law or legal process served on us; or
  * we believe it is necessary to protect our rights or property.

We may use your information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business partners and advertisers receive aggregate data about groups of LISTAFTERLIST users, but they will not receive information that personally identifies you.  
Please keep in mind that if you post content in public areas on LISTAFTERLIST, such as, online message boards, you understand that other online users may obtain access to any information you provide.  
In the event that ownership of LISTAFTERLIST was to change as a result of a merger or acquisition by another company, your information may be transferred to the acquiring company for the purpose of providing ongoing LISTAFTERLIST services to you.

**Cookies**

LISTAFTERLIST may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies in combination with your information to:

  * improve and personalize your experience on LISTAFTERLIST;
  * improve offerings that may be of interest to you;
  * to help authenticate you when you sign in to use LISTAFTERLIST;
  * to remember your preferences and registration information;
  * to help measure and research the effectiveness of LISTAFTERLIST offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and
  * to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through LISTAFTERLIST.

**Advertising Networks**

We and our advertisers may from time to time use advertising network providers, to help present advertisements on LISTAFTERLIST. These advertising networks use cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies on your computer in order to provide targeted advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you while visiting other Web sites. LISTAFTERLIST may share certain information about you as a user that is not personally identified to you (such as user age and zip code) with certain advertising network providers in order to help them deliver more relevant advertisements through their ad networks. The use of cookies, web beacons, or similar technologies by ad network providers is subject to their own privacy policies. We encourage you to return to this section periodically for updated information about advertising networks and the choices that you have about these technologies.

**Third Party Sites**

This privacy policy does not apply to other third party web sites that you may visit. These sites will have their own and separate privacy policies.

**Your Choices**

LISTAFTERLIST allows you to access and edit your registration, billing or shipping information (if applicable) in the My Profile area on the service. We will give you a choice on whether or not you want to opt-out or unsubscribe from receiving commercial e-mails from us. Keep in mind, however, that any opt-out mechanisms that we will provide do not apply to e-mails relating to notices about LISTAFTERLIST services and software, or emails confirming or informing you about your transactions with us. We encourage you to review this privacy policy periodically for any updates on other choices that we may provide to you from time to time on how your information may be used by us.

**Security**  
LISTAFTERLIST take steps to prevent the misuse of your information. You will have the ability to select and use a password to help prevent the unauthorized access your account information by others; however, we cannot guarantee that your information will never be disclosed as a result of unauthorized or illegal acts of third parties.

**Minors**  
LISTAFTERLIST is intended for a general audience, and children under the age of thirteen are not permitted to register with LISTAFTERLIST.  
How to Contact Us  
If you have any questions or concerns about LISTAFTERLIST’s Privacy Policy or its implementation, you may contact us at this email address: [privacyquestions@LISTAFTERLIST.com](mailto:privacyquestions@LISTAFTERLIST.com "Privacy Policy Questions")

**Changes**  
LISTAFTERLIST may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you should review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to LISTAFTERLIST’s information practices, you will be provided with appropriate online notice. You may be provided other privacy-related information in connection with your use of offerings from LISTAFTERLIST, as well as for special features and services not described in this Policy that may be introduced in the future.

**Last Updated 8-29-06**
